United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Communications, 1973-2000; VIII; 21.35 cubic ft.
  - Memorabilia, ca. 1973-2000; 9; 8.43 cubic ft.
    - Posters and other oversized materials, 11.13.80
      - "UUP.The Choice is Simple" NYEA challenge election poster, 1978 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 10)
      - "Link Scholarship Dollar$ at Work", undated (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 11)
      - "Cancelled: How Smart Can New York Be if We Keep Cutting Classes", March 1989 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 12)
      - "Cancelled: Will SUNY Be There for the Next Generation?", December 1990 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 13)
      - "If You Really Love New York, Don't Cut the SUNY Budget", February 1989 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 14)
      - "Slamming the Door at SUNY Slams the Door on Our State's Future", (distributed at Spring 1991 Delegate Assembly) (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 15)
      - "We Made a Promise to the Next Generation. Can Our State Afford to Break It?" (English and Spanish versions), February/March 1989; January 1990 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 16)
      - "Cutting SUNY is the No-Brain Approach to Solving Our State's Problems", March 1991 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 17)
      - "Short-Changing Higher Education is Bad Business", March 1991 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 18)
      - "Sign and mail this letter now. Your kids' future is at stake", ca. 1992 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 19)
      - "Under Destruction", (Stony Brook chapters funded), ca. 1992 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 20)
      - "Denied Admission", January/February 1992 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 21)
      - "New York-You Can't Have it Both Ways", January 1989 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 22)
      - "VOTE/COPE and UUP Together", undated (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 23)
      - "NYSUT-UUP Growing Stronger Through VOTE/COPE", undated (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 24)
      - "State University of New York Our Future Depends on It", January 1992 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 25)
      - "SUNY's Future in Question. You Hold the Answer", May 1992 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 26)
      - SUNY-New York's Most Intelligent Investment" NYS Legislative Session Calendar 1996 (Box VIII.9.3 (11.13.80-Posters and other oversized materials), Folder 27)
    - UUP canvas bags (seven total in five different styles) (Box VIII.9.4 (VIII-Communications))
    - UUP Plattsburgh canvas bag (Box VIII.9.4 (VIII-Communications))
    - White, short-sleeve UUP t-shirt, 1 item (Box VIII.9.5 (VIII-Communications))
    - White, long-sleeve UUP t-shirt, 1 item (Box VIII.9.5 (VIII-Communications))
    - Black, short-sleeve UUP t-shirt (25th anniversary), 1 item (Box VIII.9.5 (VIII-Communications))
    - White "Infrastructure" t-shirt (2) (Box VIII.9.5 (VIII-Communications))
    - Black cap and gown used for demonstrations in 1980s (1) (Box VIII.9.5 (VIII-Communications))
    - "McCall, Cuomo, Burstein" button, 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Senator Javits" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Hospitality Academy at McCormick Place" lapel pin (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "[Nelson] Mandela for President-The People's Choice" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Proud to be a Teacher" buttons (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Convention Delegates Atlanta '88" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - AFT "A Women's Place is in Her Union" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "The Wrath of Grapes" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Boycott Grapes" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - [David] Dinkins "New Yorkers Working Together for a Better New York" button, 1989; 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Deputy Sheriff" toy badge (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Yes on Bond; No on Con" buttons (3) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - UUP logo key ring, red plastic, 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - UUP logo key ring, red plastic, 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Quinn, Schuerman, Landy Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Don't Break the Promise - Invest in SUNY" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "Handle with Care" button, 1999; 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "OUCH. Cutting $121 Million from SUNY hurts us all" buttons, 2000; 2 items (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP logo key chain flashlights (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP logo brass/marble paperweight (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "Time to Invest in SUNY" desk clock (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "Andes candies" (chocolate mint) with UUP 25th anniversary logo on wrapper (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP oval lapel pins, black and red, 6 items; one in black velvet presentation box, 5 loose (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP Vote/Cope lapel pins, blue in shape of New York State, 5 items (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP 20th Anniversary lapel pins (3) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP round lapel pin, red background and gold, 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP round lapel pins, red outline with gold, 4 items (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP lapel pin in shape of New York State (blue letters on silver), 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
      See also Box VIII.9.7, tray 4 for a sample casting of pins and history of pin creation.
    - NYSUT 25th anniversary lapel pin (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - NYSUT lapel pins, gold on black background, 2 items (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "S.O.S. Save Our SUNY" buttons (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Albany Lobbyist - Veteran of 1995 NYS Budget Campaign" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Resist Speed UPS" UUP Cortland button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "No More SUNY-cide!" UUP Plattsburgh buttons (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "I Walked the Line for UUP at Plattsburgh" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Work to Rule" buttons (3) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "UUP Works while SUNY Fiddles" buttons, 2 items, one white, one yellow (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "I'm Working Hard without a Contract" UUP buttons (3) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "I'm Working Hard without a Contract" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Working Without a New Contract" buttons (4) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Bill Scheuerman State Assembly" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Ask Me About Bob Albrecht Academic Veep" button (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Reilly and the United Team" buttons (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Galbraith, Reilly, Potter and the United Team" buttons, 2 items (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Corigliano, Scheuerman, Schroeder Vote United" button, 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - UUP ID badge neckstrap holder (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - "Don't Break the Promise - Invest in SUNY" pencils (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - UUP pencil (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - UUP ballpoint pen (1) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - UUP fine-point pens (3) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - UUP fine-point pen, 25th anniversary logo, 1 item (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - UUP 25th anniversary logo highlighters (2) (Box VIII.9.6 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - "SUNY Think of the Possibilities" cube notepad (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "OUCH. SUNY Cuts hurt us all" first aid kit, 2000; 1 item (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - UUP 25th anniversary logo luggage tag (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - UUP logo paperweight, clear plastic, 1 item (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Save SUNY - Save Public Higher Education" UUP and Student Association of State University buttons (3) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - UUP stickers, white background, 15 items (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - UUP stickers, tan background, 52 items (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP 25th anniversary logo magnets (3) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "Strengthen New York State's Future - Invest in SUNY" fortune cookie (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Delegate Assembly identification badges of Frank Maraviglia, 1988 Winter; 1990 Fall; 4 items total (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Identification badges of Frank Maraviglia, various meetings, 3 items total (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - NYSUT Higher Ed Committee of 100 identification badge and empty NYSUT identification badge holder (2 total) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP buttons, red on white, 2 items (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - UUP buttons, white on blue, 2 items (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - UUP button, black and red on white, 1 item (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Responsibility, Respect, Results, Lessons for Life NYSUT/AFT Because We Care" button, 1 item (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Solidarity Day" button, September 19, 1981, AFL-CIO, NYSUT, 1 item (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Our Dream..Don't Take it Away Support SUNY" button (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "New York Works Because We Work!" buttons, CSEA, PEF, Council 82, and UUP, 2 items (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "UUP: Retain Not Retrench" button (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Vote Yes for SUNY Restorations" buttons (4) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "UUP/NYSUT VOTE/COPE Contributor" buttons (3) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "We're Bleeding" button (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "100% Restorations for SUNY" buttons (3), Undated (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Fair Taxes Recovery is Everybody's Business" button (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "Stop Parking Fees" CSEA button (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - "No Parking Fee" buttons (5); "Free Parking" button (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 3)
    - 1989 Winter Delegate Assembly ice scraper (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - UUP lapel pin in form of New York State: framed sample casting, gold-wash sample pin, pewter-washed pin, with explanatory text provided by Edward J. Alfonsin (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - Delegate identification badges with ribbons, of Frank Maraviglia (2); "This Transaction Made Possible By SUNY" stack of 100 "dollar bills" (1) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 4)
    - "Elect Kennison and Abraham Now" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Corigliano, Scheuerman, Reddy Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Corigliano, Scheuerman, Kowal Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Corigliano, Scheuerman, Albrecht, Bird Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Kowal, Scheuerman, Landy Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Corigliano, Scheuerman, Hunt and the United Team" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Floss Everyday It Works" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Matthews, Scheuerman, Hunt and the United Team" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Floss, Marino, Blackman-Stroud Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Smith, Matthews, Blackman-Stroud Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Matthews, Albrecht, Blackman-Stroud Vote United" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - "Ed Quinn MDO" button (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 5)
    - Baseball caps (3): UUP (maroon); UUP 25th anniversary logo (black); UUP (white) (Box VIII.9.7 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Vote Maraviglia" Styrofoam hat (1) (Box VIII.9.8 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - UUP Plattsburgh baseball cap (1) (Box VIII.9.8 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, College at Oneonta, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, Oswego, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, Delhi, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, Maritime College, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, Stony Brook, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, Binghamton, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York, New Paltz, 1 item (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: SUNY Morrisville (1) (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup: State University of New York at Buffalo (1) (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - "Invest in Futures" baby bottle (proposed legislative giveaway design; not actually used) (1) (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "SUNY: Invest in Futures" glow in the dark teddy bear "piggy banks" (final legislative giveaway design) (4) (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - "SUNY: Handle with Care" legislative giveaway coffee mug (1) (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Slides: Operation Safeguard SUNY, 1997 December (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Slide Box (Box VIII.9.9 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
      Containing:
      A. Slides: Ernest Boyer (SUNY Chancellor) (12 slides)
      B. Slides from "Archives Room" display (80 slide)
      C. Loose slides from "Memorabilia" boxes, probably from "Archives Room" display (101 slides)
      See box itself for additional information on the "Archives Room" slides and for identification information for the individual slides.
    - Coffee cup, State University of New York, Health Science Center at Syracuse, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, State University of New York, Farmingdale, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, SUNY, College at Purchase, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, Potsdam College, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, State University of New York, College of Arts and Science at Geneseo, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, University at Albany, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, State University of New York, Institute of Technology, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, Alfred State College, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, State University of New York, College at Fredonia, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 1)
    - Coffee cup, Brockport College, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Coffee cup, College of Agriculture and Technology (chipped), 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Coffee cup, UUP-Vote/Cope, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Coffee cup, UUP Stony Brook, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Coffee cup, UUP Albany Chapter, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)
    - Coffee cup, UUP Oneonta Chapter, 1 item (Box VIII.9.10 (VIII-Communications), Tray 2)